Problem?
怎么了?
- This is Thai food.
- Here we go.
- 这是泰国菜
- 又来了
We don't have Thai food on
Thursday. We have pizza on Thursday.
周四不该吃泰国菜 应该吃披萨
Yes, but we all agreed that the third Thursday of
every month would be Anything Can Happen Thursday.
是啊 但我们一致同意
每月第三个周四是随心所欲日
Well, apparently the news
didn't reach my digestive system,
显然没通知我的消化系统
which, when startled, has it's own
version of Anything Can Happen Thursday.
它一震惊 就开始自己随心所欲了
Come on, the whole idea behind
Anything Can Happen Thursday
拜托 随心所欲日的目的
is to get out of this
rut we've been in lately.
就是要打破常规
Rut? I think you mean "consistency."
常规? 你是说"连续性"吧
And if we're going to abandon that,
then why even call it Thursday?
如果想要抛弃常规 干啥还叫周四呢?
Let's call it "Quonko Day" and divide
it into 29 hours of 17 minutes apiece,
何不改成"Quonko日" 每天29小时17分
and celebrate it by sacrificing
a goat to the mighty god Ra.
杀头山羊向上神献祭来庆祝
I could go for some goat.
我能弄到山羊
Sheldon, wagreed we'd do
something different tonight.
Sheldon 说好今晚做点别的
All right. Let's go to
the comic book store.
好啊 一起去漫画书店吧
We went to the comic
book store last night.
昨晚刚去过啊
Last night was Wednesday.
昨晚是周三
Wednesday is comic book night.
周三是漫画之夜
Tonight, we'll be going on Thursday,
because it's Anything Can Happen Thursday.
今晚算是周四去 因为今天是随心所欲日
Way to think outside but pressed
right up against the box, Sheldon.
思维跳跃 打破常规啊 Sheldon
So what are we going to do tonight?
今晚到底要做什么呢?
If I may proffer a suggestion, in bars
all across this great nation of ours,
容我建议 你看全国各地酒吧里
Thursday night is Ladies' Night.
周四是美女之夜
Which means, as the evening progresses,
也就是说 随着黑夜越深
we will get better looking courtesy of 99
cent margaritas and two-for-one Jell-O shots.
拿着99美分的龙舌兰和买一送一的果冻饮
我们能更有魅力
Come on, Howard, the odds of us picking
up girls in a bar are practically zero.
拜托 Howard 咱们泡到美女的几率为零
Oh, really? Are you familiar
with the Drake Equation?
真的吗 你知道德瑞克方程吗?
The one that estimates the odds of
making contact with extraterrestrials
那个通过计算一系列严格限制的小数乘积
by calculating the product of an increasingly
restrictive series of fractional values
例如有行星的星系和可能产生生命的行星
such as those stars with planets, and
those planets likely to develop life?
得出接触外星生物几率的方程式?
N equals R times FP times NE
times FL times FI times FC times L?
N=R*FP*NE*FL*FI*FC*L?
Yeah, that one.
就这个
You can modify it to calculate
our chances of having sex
可以修改一下 用来计算我们艳遇的几率
by changing the formula to use the
number of single women in Los Angeles,
只需改用洛杉矶单身女性数量
the number of those who might find us attractive,
and what I call the Wolowitz Coefficient.
会对我们一见钟情的人的数量
还有Wolowitz系数
The Wolowitz Coefficient?
Wolowitz系数?
Neediness times dress size squared.
需求度乘以衣服紧身度的平方
Crunching the numbers, I come up with a
conservative 5,812 potential sex partners
通过计算 40英里之内 保守估计
within a 40-mile radius.
有5812个潜在对象
You're joking.
开玩笑吧
I'm a horny engineer, Leonard.
我是饥渴的工程师 Leonard
I never joke about math or sex.
对于数字和做爱 我从不玩笑
Well, what are we waiting
for? Let's bounce, bitches.
那还等什么 放马过来吧 小妞
Well, you're right.
说的没错
It's Anything Can Happen Thursday.
Let's hit the clubs and meet hot women!
今天是随心所欲日 我们去泡吧泡妞吧
Here we go. Lock up your daughters!
来吧 把你女儿锁起来!
We're going to hit it and quit it.
咱们速战速决
Or we could finish eating and
go to the comic book store.
或者我们可以吃完饭 去逛逛漫画店
Also a good plan.
也是个好主意
All right, but next Anything Can Happen
Thursday, we're definitely going to a bar.
好吧 但下次随心所欲日
我们一定要去酒吧
Oh, absolutely.
那必然
You heard that, Ladies' Night ladies?
听到没 美女之夜的美女?
We're eventually coming for you!
哥哥们要来咯!
Fascinating.
真赞
荣誉出品
翻译: 王 饭特稀 冰啤梨果橙
校对: penny
时间轴: 咔肉肉
Oh, hey, guys. Where're you headed?
嘿 你们要去哪?
To the comic book store.
去漫画店
You're probably thinking, "The
comic book store? On a Thursday?
你准在想 周四去漫画店?
Why, I've fallen down the rabbit
hole and into a land of madness."
怎么会呢 天方夜谭啊
What you have failed to take into account, Penny,
is that this is Anything Can Happen Thursday.
Penny 你百密一疏
没想到今天是随心所欲日
You got me.
真了解我
Oh, hey, while you're there, could pick
me up a few comics for my nhew's birthday?
对了 能否买几本连环画回来
我想送小侄子做生日礼物
I think you mean comic books.
你是说漫画书吧
Comics are feeble attempts at
humor featuring talking babies
连环画是那些"逗你一笑"栏目里
and anthropomorphized pets found traditionally
in the optimistically-named "funny pages."
会说话的婴儿
和人格化的动物讲述的冷笑话
Leonard, could you pick me up a
few comics for my nephew's birthday?
Leonard 你能帮忙买吗?
Sure. What does he like?
没问题 他喜欢什么?
I don't know, he's 13.
Just pick out anything.
我也不知道 他13了 看着买吧
Just pick out anything?
看着买?
Well, maybe at the same time we can pick out
a new suit for him without knowing his size.
那不知道尺寸 也能买衣服咯
Or pick out his career for him
without knowing his aptitude.
不知道他的本事 也能给他找工作咯
Or pick out a new breakfast cereal
without knowing his fiber requirements...
不知道纤维素需求 也能给他挑麦片咯
or his feelings about
little marshmallows.
或者不知道他是否喜欢软糖
Spider-Man. Get
him Spider-Man.
蜘蛛侠 就买蜘蛛侠吧
Amazing Spider-Man, Ultimate
Spider-Man, Spectacular Spider-Man,
非凡蜘蛛侠 终极蜘蛛侠 神奇蜘蛛侠
The Marvelous Adventures of
Spider-Man, Spider-Man 2099?
蜘蛛侠大冒险 还是蜘蛛侠2099
Leonard?
You know this can go on all night.
Why don't you just come with us?
这样说起来就没完了 跟我们走吧?
That's what I was trying to avoid.
我就怕这个
Oh, I forgot Sensational Spider-Man.
哦对 还有感动蜘蛛侠
Aw, what a cute, little store.
小店好可爱啊
Ev-everybody's staring at me.
大家都在看我
Don't worry, they're more scared
of you than you are of them.
别担心 其实他们更害怕
Unlikely.
未必吧
Here, what about this one for my nephew?
买这个送我侄子怎么样?
- A superb choice.
- Oh, great.
- 好眼光
- 哦 太好了
Provided he has already
read Infinite Crisis and 52,
前提是他看过了无限危机和52
and is familiar with the
reestablishment of the DC multiverse.
并且熟悉DC多重世界的重建
What's a "multiverse"?
嘛叫"多重世界"?
Get her out of here.
快请她出去
Come on, I'll help you pick something.
来吧 我来帮你选
That's right. She's with us.
没错 她跟我们来的
Guys like that are so pathetic.
那种男生太可悲了
Tell me about it.
还用说
Ooh, look, a new Batman belt buckle.
快看 新版蝙蝠侠腰带扣
Oh, hey, Lnard. Can I
help you find something?
嘿 Leonard 用不用我帮你?
Oh, he Stuart. This is Penny. She's
just looking for some comic books.
嘿 Stuart 这是Penny 她想买漫画
Oh, really, wow. Blink twice if
you're here against your will.
真的啊 如果你是被逼来了 就眨两下眼
I think we're fine, Stuart.
我们自己挑吧 Stuart
Okay. Well, let me know
if you need anything.
好的 需要帮忙就说话哈
Thks.
谢谢
Oh, he seems like a nice guy.
哦 他人挺不错啊
You mean for someone
who's into comic books?
你是说作为一个漫画迷?
No. No-no-no. I just
meant for... yeah.
不不不 我的意思是...没错
Penny, just because people appreciate
comic books doesn't make them weirdos.
Penny 喜欢漫画不等于是怪人
Stuart's a terrific artist.
Stuart是个不错的艺术家
He went to the Rhode
Island School of Design.
在罗德岛设计学院就读
Okay, what about the guy over there in the
superhero T-shirt tucked into his sweatpants?
好吧 把美国队长T恤放运动裤里的那人呢?
Uh, yeah, that's Captain Sweatpants.
啊 那是运动裤船长
He doesn't really help the
point I'm trying to make.
他确实没法验证我的论点
- Got it.
- 有了
Need it!
这个!
Let it go, Sheldon.
放手 Sheldon
Why should I let go? I saw it first.
为什么要我放手? 我先看见的
Yes, but I saw it from the front.
没错 可我看到的是正面
A far less impressive feat.
完全没有说服力
Oh, come on! I need this
for my Batman collection.
噢 算了吧! 我要凑齐一套蝙蝠侠
Well, I need it for my Robin collection.
而我要凑齐一套罗宾
Rock-Paper-Scissors-
Lizard-Spock?
石头剪子布蜥蜴史波克?
Why would I gamble? It's mine. Let go.
干嘛猜拳? 这是我的 松手
- You let go.
- No, you!
- 你松手
- 不 你松手!
- No, you!
- Problem?
- 不 你松手!
- 有事吗?
Yes. He won't let go of my comic book.
嗯 他拿着我的漫画不放
It's my comic book!
是我的漫画!
Leonard, we need a ruling.
Leonard 你来裁决吧
Cut it in half?
一人一半?
Excuse me.
打扰一下
Oh, hello again.
噢 又见面了
What would you recommend as a
present for a 13-year-old boy?
送什么给13岁的小男孩做生日礼物好呢?
A 13-year-old
girl.
13岁的小女孩咯
But if you're dead set on
a comic book, try... this.
不过要是你死抱着漫画不放的话
你可以试试... 这个
Oh, Hellblazer. What's this about?
噢 地狱神探 什么内容呀?
A morally ambiguous confidence
man who smokes, has lung cancer
一个道德有问题的自信男人
爱抽烟 有肺癌
and is tormented by the
spirits of the undead.
被不死亡灵折磨的故事
Well, if that doesn't make me the
favorite aunt, I don't know what will.
哦 要是他连这都不喜欢
那我这个阿姨真是没辙了
Is this me?
这是我吗?
Depends. Do you like it?
看情况了 你喜欢么?
Wow, it's really good.
喔 画得真好
Yes, that's you.
没错 是你
Thats so sweet, but
what if I didn't like it?
嘴真甜 那要是我不喜欢呢?
It'd still be you, but
I'd feel like an idiot.
还是你咯 不过我就成傻瓜了
I don't believe it.
难以置信
Stuart's putting the moves on Penny.
Stuart和Penny搞上了
I have got to learn how to draw.
我要学画画
Once again, defeated by
your own prurient interests.
再次被你的色心打败了
Guys, have you seen Stuart all
up in Penny's siness over there?
小子 看见那边没?
Stuart把Penny给包办了
Nobody's up in anybody's business.
谁也没把谁包办咯
Let's just buy our stuff and go.
我们买完东西就走人
Okay, you've got my number.
好咧 电话号码已经给你了
Now, give me the picture.
快把画像给我
You drive a hard bargain.
你可真会讨价还价
But here.
给
All right. So, um, just give me a call.
好耶 那么... 给我打电话噢
So, Leonard, how are you enjoying
Anything Can Happen Thursday?
Leonard 你觉得随心所欲日怎么样啊?
Look at that. That's a dent.
瞧瞧 凹进去了
Thank you, Howard
"Ham-Fisted" Wolowitz.
多谢了 Howard "笨手笨脚" Wolowitz
Did you just shut the TV off in the middle
of the classic Deep Space Nine/Star Trek:
你看了一半的星际旅行/深空九号:
经典交叉集特辑
The Original Series Trouble
With Tribbles ossover episode?
就把电视给关了?
Apparently so.
显然是咯
Are you ill?
你病了?
No.
没有
All right.
那好
Then is it fair to say that you're
experiencing some sort of emotional turmoil
那说你因为今晚早些时候Penny那事
over the events involving
Penny earlier this evening?
感情出现波动不过分吧
When did you pick up on that?
你啥时候知道的?
A moment ago, when you turned off the TV in the
middle of the classic Deep Space Nine/Star Trek:
就刚刚啊 你看了一半的
星际旅行/深空九号经典交叉特辑
The Original Series Trouble
With Tribbles crossover episode.
就把电视给关掉了
Would you like some advice?
要我给点意见吗?
Sure, why not?
好啊 说说无妨
Well then, thiis the perfect time to launch
a blog with an interactive comments section?
你不觉得现在开个有互动留言版的
部落格正是时候吗?
Gee, thanks a lot.
真是多谢了
Would you rather I offer
my personal insight?
你要我说说自己的看法?
I don't need any insights.
我不需要任何人的看法
I just want to know why Penny's
more interested in Stuart than me.
我只是想知道Penny对Stuart的兴趣
怎么就比对我的大拉摸多咧
We're practically the same guy.
我们简直就是同一个人
Oh, I disagree.
噢 恕难同意
Stuart is taller, artistic,
self-employed and, most significantly,
Stuart比你高 有艺术气息
自己当老板 当然最重要的是
he gets 45 percent off comic books.
他买漫画能打55折
You're right. I really should be
asking strangers on the Internet.
你说得对 我是该上网问问那些陌生人
My original point.
我就说嘛
Chinese food, vintage video games...
中餐 骨灰级电子游戏
After the nightmare
ofnything Can Happen Thursday,
在随心所欲日的恶梦之后
this is Friday night the
way it was meant to be.
周五终于回归它的原样了
Who's up for Sheldon-Free Saturday?
有谁赞成周六把Sheldon踢开?
Oh, hey, guys.
噢 你们好啊
Hey, Penny... and Stuart.
嘿 Penny... 还有Stuart
Hey, Stuart.
嘿 Stuart
- Hey, guys.
- So what are you kids up to?
- 你们好
- 你们俩上哪儿去?
Stuart has a piece in an art
show that's opening tonight.
Stuart有件作品参展 今晚开幕了
And you guys are going
together. Great...
你们俩就一起去了 真棒...
It is great. Really
great. Freaking awesome.
是啊 真棒 爽歪歪了
What are you guys doing?
你们干啥呢?
It's Friday night-- that means Chinese
food and vintage video gas, right?
礼拜五晚上咯 无非是中餐
还有骨灰级电子游戏 对吧?
Vintage doesn't even begin to
describe what we have planned.
我们准备的绝对不止骨灰级
Tonight, we are playing the classic
1980 interactive text adventure, Zork.
今晚我们要玩的是上世纪八十年代
经典的互动文字冒险游戏 魔域
(有史以来首个文字冒险游戏)
It's the buggy beta version.
第二版哦 BUG超多
Wow, Zork. Well, you guys have fun.
喔 魔域啊 你们玩得开心哦
Yeah.
那是
- See you guys.
- See you, Stuart.
- 回见
- 回见 Stuart
- Hey, Howard?
- Yes?
- 嘿 Howard?
- 什么事?
Take me to a bar with women.
带我去个有女人的酒吧
- Really?
- Yeah.
- 真的假的?
- 那还有假
Okay!
好耶!
Let me just go inside
and slip off my underwear.
等我一会儿 我进去把内裤脱了
Why?
为啥?
Well, if I get lucky, I don't want
to be caught in my Aquaman briefs.
要是走运的话 我可不想被她
看到我穿着水行侠的内裤
Do you... Let's go.
你呢... 走吧
May I have a grasshopper with
a little umbrella, please?
来一杯绿色蚱蜢 要撑把小伞的
- No, he may not.
- Why?
- 不 他不要了
- 为什么?
I'm not sitting here with a guy drinking
a grasshopper with a little umbrella.
我才不要跟喝撑把小伞的
绿色蚱蜢的家伙坐在一起
Fine. I'll have a chocolate martini.
行 那我要巧克力马提尼
Wrong again!
又错了!
Come on, you know I can't talk to women unless
I'm lit up like the Hindu festival of Devali.
算了吧 你知道我只有像过排灯节那样
被点得金亮亮才能和女人说话啊
Look, there are plenty of bars in Los Angeles where
you can order grasshoppers and chocolate martinis,
听着 整个洛杉矶有无数酒吧
你尽可以点绿色蚱蜢或者巧克力马提尼
but you wouldn't have to because
there are no women in them.
但那根本没必要
因为里头压根没有女人
Gotcha.
了解
I'll have a Brandy Alexander.
那给我来一杯白兰地亚历山大
All right, the Three Musketeers
just became the Dynamic Duo.
好吧 三个火枪手变成了活力双雄
(来自)
- Should we talk to some of these women?
- No.
- 我们应该找这些女人聊聊吗?
- 不
It's way too early
in the night for that.
这对于今晚来说还太早了点
See, first we let the lawyers and
the jocks thin the herd, and then...
这样 我们先让那些律师 运动员什么的
缩小猎物范围 然后...
we go after the weak
and the old and the lame.
我们就去追他们挑剩下的老弱病残
That's your system?
这就是你的泡妞方式?
That's my system.
对 这是我的独门秘方
Oh, and if you spot a chick with
a Seeing Eye dog, she's mine.
噢对了 如果你看到一个牵着
导盲犬的少妇 她是我的
Oh, come on.
噢 拜托
I think it's nice that Captain
Sweatpants showed up to your art opening.
我觉得"运动裤船长"出现在
你的艺术展上挺好呀
Yeah, it would have been nicer if
he hadn't touched all the cheese.
对 如果他不把奶酪摸个遍就更好了
You know, it's kind of early.
嗯 现在时间还有点早
Do you want to maybe come in
for some coffee or something?
你想进来喝杯咖啡什么的吗?
Oh, gee, it's a little
late for coffee, isn't it?
现在喝咖啡好像有点晚了 不是吗
Oh, you think "coffee," means
coffee. That is so sweet.
噢 你觉得"咖啡"就是指咖啡
真是个小可爱
Come on. I think I have decaf.
来吧 我有不含咖啡因的"咖啡"
Oh, good. Stuart. I
thought I heard your voice.
噢 太好了 Stuart
我觉得刚才是听到你说话来着
Do you have a moment?
你现在有时间吗?
Uh, yeah, I guess.
呃 有 我想
Sheldon, we're a little busy here, so...
Sheldon 我们现在有点忙 所以...
- What are you doing?
- We're having coffee.
- 你们要干什么?
- 我们要喝点咖啡
Well, isn't it a little late for coffee?
不觉得现在喝咖啡有点晚么?
It's okay. She thinks she has decaf.
没关系 她说她有无咖啡因的
I'll just go look for it.
我现在进去找找看
What's up?
什么事?
Well, I've spent the last three hours in an
online debate in the DC Comics Batman chatroom,
我刚才花了三个小时在DC漫画
蝙蝠侠聊天室网上辩论
- and I need your help.
- Oh, yeah. Those guys can be very stubborn.
- 我需要你帮忙
- 噢 我了解 那帮家伙有时非常顽固
What's the topic?
你们辩论的主题是?
I am asserting, in the event that
Batman's death proves permanent,
我坚持认为 当蝙蝠侠长眠于世之后
the original Robin, Dick Grayson, is
the logical successor to the Bat Cowl.
逻辑上讲 第一代罗宾 Dick Grayson
应该是蝙蝠侠战衣的继承者
Sheldon, I'm afraid you
couldn't be more wrong.
Sheldon 恐怕你不能错的更厉害了
More wrong?
错的更厉害?
Wrong is an absolute state
and not subject to gradation.
错误是一个绝对的状态
你不能对它进行程度上的划分
Of course it is. It'a little wrong
to say a tomato is a vegetable.
当然可以 说番茄是一种蔬菜
就是有一点点错误
It's very wrong to say
it's a suspension bridge.
如果说它是一座吊桥
那就是严重的错误
But returning to the original
issue, Dick Grayson became Nightwing,
回到刚才的事情上
Dick Grayson后来成了夜翔
a superhero in his own right.
自立门户的英雄
Batman 2 has to be the
second Robin, Jason Todd.
于是蝙蝠侠2里就出现了
第二代罗宾 Jason Todd
Has to be? Has to be?
一定要这样吗? 一定要吗?
I hope you're being
deliberately provocative.
我希望你只是在故意煽动和挑拨
I found the decaf!
我找到脱咖啡因咖啡了!
Oh, great!
噢 太棒了!
Herbal tea for me, please.
给我来杯花草茶 谢谢
Barkeep! Alexander me.
老板! 来杯亚历山大
How about those two?
那两个怎么样?
No... They're eating peanuts.
不... 他们在吃花生
And my allergies, one kiss would
put me in Cedars-Sinai for a week.
我的花生过敏症 一个吻就足够送我到
Cedars-Sinai医疗中心呆上一个礼拜
What about the ones in the corner?
角落里那些如何?
Possible. Very possible.
还不错 非常不错
Do you want the one in the whiplash
collar or the one who keeps blinking?
你想要那个戴着颈椎围脖的还是那个
不停眨眼睛的?
- I think Blinky's cute.
- You got it, sir.
- 我觉得眨眼睛那个挺可爱的
- 好吧 先生
Wait, so we just go over there?
等等 那我们就这么直接过去了?
No. We have a little ep work to do.
不 我们还有些准备工作要做
Put this in your mouth. We walk
past them, you stumble a bit.
把这个放进嘴巴里 然后我们走过去
你假装走的有点踉跄和摇晃
I say, sorry, my friend's
had a little too much.
我就说 对不起 我朋友有点喝多了
And then I start to pull
it out of your mouth.
然后我就从你嘴里把这个拉出来
And say, "A little too much fun."
接着说 "嘿 太有趣了"
Get it? I mean, they're
laughing. We're laughing.
明白吗? 我是说 他们会大笑 我们也笑
Then we get them up to about a . 15 blood
alcohol level, and tell them we're millionaires.
给她们灌点酒 让血液酒精含量达到0.15
接着就告诉她们我们是百万富翁...
What else you got?
还有啥别的招不?
Depends. Are you willing to sit on my lap
and pretend to be a ventriloquist dummy?
见机行事呗 你愿意坐我大腿上
假装口技表演者操纵的傀儡吗?
No.
不
I can't sit on your lap.
You don't know the routine.
我不能坐在你大腿上
你不知道都该怎么演
I'm sorry, but you're obviously stuck in a pre
- Zero Hour DC universe.
非常抱歉 但你的思维明显只是
停留在DC漫画"前零时"时代
Of course I am.
我当然是
Removing Joe Chill as the killer of Batman's parents
effectively deprived him of his raison d'etre.
如果Joe Chill不是害蝙蝠侠杀父母仇人
那就等于剥夺了他继续存在的意义
Okay. You can throw all the French around
you want, it doesn't make you right.
好吧 你可以继续拽你的法文
但那不表示你的理论就是对的
Au contraire.
恰恰相反(法语)
Plus, you're forgetting that the Infinite Crisis
storyline restored Joe Chill to the Batman mythology.
另外 你忘了在系列里
Joe Chill又重新回归蝙蝠侠传奇
I am forgetting nothing
and I resent your tone.
我没忘记任何事儿
另外 我讨厌你的语气
Okay. Look, Sheldon, it's late.
I've got to get some sleep.
好吧 瞧 Sheldon 时间挺晚了
我得回去睡觉了
So, I win.
所以 是我赢了
No, I'm tired.
当然不 我只是太累了
So, I win.
所以 我赢了
- Fine. You win.
- Darn tootin', I win.
- 好吧 你赢了
- 没错 我赢了
Penny, I really had a terrific time...
Penny 我刚刚玩的很开心
Penny?
No, no, no, no, no. Don't wake her.
不 不 不 别叫醒她
She'll maul you like a rabid wolverine.
她会像一只狂暴的狼獾撕裂你的皮肉
You know, I don't think that was decaf.
我想刚才那杯可不是脱咖啡因的咖啡
Wait. Is this your card or isn't it?
等等 这张牌是你们的吗?
Trust me. This was their card.
相信我 这张是她们的牌
I thought you were good at this.
我以为你很擅长这个
You're always talking about how
you go to bars and meet women.
你总是高谈阔论你怎么去酒吧泡妞
I do, all the time.
我的确一直这么干
Well, what happened? We've
been sitting here all night
那到底是怎么回事?
在这坐了一晚上
and the longest conversation you've had
with a woman was when your mom called.
你和女人最长的一次谈话
是跟你妈妈讲电话
You're just going to make me
come out and say it, aren't you?
你这是要逼我说出来 是吗
Say what?
说什么?
You're weighing me down.
是你拖累了我
I'm a falcon who hunts better solo.
我是一只更适合独自捕猎的猎鹰
Fine. I'll sit here.
You take flight and hunt.
那好吧 我就坐在这儿
你自己飞走 寻找猎物吧
Don't be ridiculous. You can't
just tell a falcon when to hunt.
别逗了 哪轮到你告诉猎鹰啥时候狩猎啊
Actually, you can.
事实上 可以
There's whole sport built around it.
这旁边都是训练场地
Falconry.
猎鹰训练师
Shut up. Let's just
get Koothrappali and go.
闭嘴 我们去找Koothrappali然后闪人
Lucky bastard.
这个幸运的混蛋
It's got to be that
stupid accent of his.
肯定是他那愚蠢的口音起了作用
Hello. I am Sanjay Wolowitz from Bombay.
嗨 我是印度孟买来的Sanjay Wolowitz
Okay, I'm stumped.
好吧 我彻底懵了
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负